https://www.thelion.com/bin/privacy.cgi

Fri 12/11/2020 08:09 ETDJIA29999.2669.000.23%TELCO180.053.151.75%GOLD1834.162.020.11%Shanghai3338.6934.391.03%S&P 5003668.104.770.13%BANKS419.912.270.54%OIL46.840.060.13%BITCOIN17850.79123.170.69%NASDAQ12405.8166.990.54%PHARM654.691.110.17%US/EU1.210.000.11%Futures3642.0026.590.73%
HomeForumPortfolioNewsUserMailHelpAIO Msg Search:
Welcome Stranger!  Please sign up or log in to enable additional features.Sign Up | Mail | Log In
User - Privacy
Protecting Your
Personal Privacy
TheLion.com
is strongly committed to protecting and respecting the privacy of its
users. The purpose of this privacy statement is to assure you that when
visiting TheLion.com, we would never sell or compromise your personal
information before gaining your permission. Please read the following
to fully understand how TheLion.com is committed in making our
members feel comfortable with submitting personal information on our website.
This statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire website.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, feel free
to contact thelionwwwsite@gmail.com
Use of electronic cookies
Before you post a
message in one of our exciting message boards, you can choose to enable
"cookie". A cookie is a small data file that contain bits of information
that Web sites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record keeping
purposes. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information
you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read
cookie files created by other sites. TheLion.com uses cookies for
allowing our members to post messages without going through the hassle
of logging in every time.
Use of Information
TheLion.com will only use any information voluntarily you give
us to help us improve our sites. We track what our users like and don't
like about our web sites, but not what they read.
Disclosure
TheLion.com reserves the right to access and disclose individually
identifiable information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government
requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself or its
users. Where practical, TheLion.com will attempt to obtain the
prior consent of the individual prior to disclosing individually identifiable
information.
What Else Should
You Know About Your Privacy?
Please remember that whenever you disclose personal information publicly,
for example, on message boards or through email, that information can
be collected and used by others. At the same time, if you post personal
information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited
messages from other parties in return. If you don't want strangers to
send you email, don't post your email address on a message board. Furthermore,
while we do our best to protect your personal information, TheLion.com
can not guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us,
and you do so at your own risk. Basically, there are constantly people
out there trying to obtain personal information about you without your
consent. You must protect yourself. You are responsible for maintaining
the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be
very careful and responsible whenever you're online.
TheLion.com | About Us | Agreement & Disclaimer | Privacy |
Twitter© 2020- TheLion.com, Inc.
